Dad?
Ted,
tomorrow's your
grandfather's birthday.
You haven't been
home in years.
You think you can come back tomorrow?
Yeah, Dad, I'm...
so sorry. I've...
been so caught
up with work
the past couple
years. Hmm...
I'll definitely make it
back tomorrow.
Great.
I'll be waiting
for you, son.
Okay, bye.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
It's just, uh,
my grandpa's
birthday tomorrow.
I haven't seen
them in a long time.
Well, I know that
they're gonna be really happy to see you.
You know...
Uhm.
I was thinking, um,
if you're not
busy tomorrow,
like, if you don't
have any plans,
maybe you could
come with me.
Or I could introduce
you to them.
Well...
You want to introduce me to your family?
I mean, we might
make a good team.
What do you think?
Hmm.
Yeah, you'd be a good sidekick, I think.
Oh, I'd be the sidekick?
I might be the star.
Would you be
okay if that's
how this worked out,
if it works out?
Hmm. I guess
we'll be two stars.
I'll take that.
Two stars.
Then I better
get some gifts.
Well, if you do...
Nothing too
expensive, okay?
No, it is my first time meeting them,
and I have to make a good impression.
Actually, I'm
gonna go right now
and have Emily
help me pick out
some good gifts.
Okay.
And maybe,
after you win
the championship,
I'll give you
my special gift.
It's been a while.
I just hope you're
doing okay, Dad.